Centuries before the exploration of space, there
was another voyage into the unknown.
1492: Conquest of Paradise is a action, adventure,
drama film directed by Ridley Scott.
1492: Conquest of Paradise depicts Christopher Columbus’ discovery of
The New World and his effect on the indigenous people.
Christopher Columbus, played by Gérard Depardieu.
Sanchez, played by Armand Assante.
Queen Isabella, played by Sigourney Weaver.
Older Fernando, played by Loren Dean.
Beatrix, played by Ángela Molina.
Marchena, played by Fernando Rey.
1492: Conquest of Paradise is a 1992 epic historical drama film directed by Ridley Scott, written by
Roselyne Bosch and starring Gérard Depardieu, Armand Assante, and Sigourney Weaver.
It portrays the travels to the New World by the Italian explorer
Christopher Columbus and the effect this had on Indigenous peoples.
The film was released to celebrate the 500th anniversary of Columbus' voyage.
It debuted less than two months after the film Christopher Columbus: The
Discovery, often leading to confusion between the two.
The film received mixed reviews, with particular criticism
aimed at the film's historical inaccuracies.
The film explores themes of indigenous, the new world,
discovery of america, native american, 15th century.
The tone is emotional.